<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-09T09:23:41+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">The Mast-Head</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-mast-head/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Mast-Head" /><published>2021-12-08T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-12-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-mast-head</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-mast-head/">&lt;!-- Write from here your post !!! --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the very first post of this blog. This is not the first blog I’ve ever written though, far from it. I’ve been writing
blogs on and off for many years now. However, none of my previous blogs has really stuck. After a few years, sometimes
even just a few months, I’ve always ended up abandoning them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why am I starting a new one now? Paradoxically, because of a need to detox from technology, more specifically from
social media. I would like to stop wasting time browing Instagram timelines and liking random photos, and start
concentrating more on reading, yoga, writing, and other things that really matter in life. Hence this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In it, I plan to write about anything I am inspired to share with the world, so to speak, so this will not be a themed
blog. My interests include Literature, knitting, yoga, planning and journalling, stationery in general, garderning,
teaching and learning languages, animal rights and veganism. So posts on ony of these topics can be expected on this
blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have selected the title and layout of the blog as a homage to one of my all-time favourite books, Herman Melville’s
&lt;em&gt;Moby-Dick&lt;/em&gt;. As I post this I am in the process of starting a research on the book, so I might even decide to publish
something on that here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you stop by and read something interesting, throught-provoking, outraging, or even just plain wrong, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://labrezza.github.io/about/&quot;&gt;contact
me&lt;/a&gt; to share your opinion. I would love it if this place could become an opportunity
to engage in conversations and exchanges of opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, until next time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blogging" /><summary type="html">This is the very first post of this blog. This is not the first blog I’ve ever written though, far from it. I’ve been writing blogs on and off for many years now. However, none of my previous blogs has really stuck. After a few years, sometimes even just a few months, I’ve always ended up abandoning them.</summary></entry></feed>